Last year the smoking tire went on the Bull Run
Live Rally in the 2010 Ford SVT Raptor. I liked
it so much, I bought one, and here it is.
We’re going back to Bull Run this year, of course,
to help from our friends at Black Magic, and we’re
so serious about it, we got two Valentine 1 radar
detectors. Oh yeah. So we’re all set up, and the
reason we got two is because we’re going to be
going a little bit faster. We got a 2011 Shelby
GT500 with a 550 horsepower all aluminum V8. We are
going to be right in the action bringing you guys
a video every single day, live from the Bull Run
Rally, July 9th to 16th. And the only place to
watch it is on BlackMagicsShine.com or right here on the
smoking tire. (upbeat music)